A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.26 (A2000) FA470
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.26 (A2000)
1969-2004 (Bulk: 1987-1998)
1987-1998
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA470
119.21 Cubic Feet
91 standard record storage boxes, R3287-R3367, R3370-R3378.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2000.
Material received in 27 accessions, as noted.
Arrangement note
Reccords are primarily arranged by Accession and the further arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Biographical/Historical note
Rockefeller Foundation
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 20 years old are open research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply.
- AC.2000.003: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1983-1999; AC.2000.003; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3287.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3287.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.003.1
    - RF 86024 - NORPLANT CONTRACEPTIVE IMPLANTS - POST-MARKETING SURVEILLANCE, 1986; 1989-1991 (Box R3287)
    - RF 88078 A 53 - SAHEL INSTITUTE- POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT FELLOWSHIPS, 1987-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3287)
    - RF 89054 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - AGRICULTURE, 1983-1996 (Box R3287)
    - RF 89057 A 115 - PAIVA. EDILSON, 1985-1995; 1999 (Box R3287)
    - RF 90025 - INTERNATIONAL BOARD FOR SOIL RESEARCH MANAGEMENT- SUSTAINABILITY, 1989-1997 (Box R3287)
- AC.2000.007: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1981-1998; AC.2000.007; 14.4 Cubic Feet 12 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3288-R3299.; 12 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3288-R3299.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.007.1
    - RF 90031 A 107 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA - WIDE HYBRID CROSSES, 1990-1997 (Box R3288)
    - 900034-82 - UNIVERSITY OF INNSBRUCK - MOLECULAR ACTION OF GOSSYPOL AT CELLULAR LEVEL, 1994-1995 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90044 - POVERTY ADVOCATES RESEARCH COUNCIL, 1989-1992 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90051 - CROP GENETIC MAPS, 1990-1991 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90059 - UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHAMPTON - PROGRAMME FOR PROMOTING NUCLEAR NON-PROLIFERATION, 1990-1996 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90075 A 3 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - RICE NODULATION ANALYSES, 1990-1997 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90075 A4 - UNIVERSITY OF NOTTINGHAM - NITROGEN FIXATION IN NON-LEGUMES, 1990-1997 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90078 A 90 - HALL INSTITUTE-MULTIDISCIPLINARY APPROACH TO PHILIPPINE SCHISTOSOMIASIS, 1988-1994 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90079 - RESEARCH AND POLICY BOARDS, 1987-1989 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3288)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3289)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3290)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3291)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3292)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3293)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3294)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3295)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3296)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3297)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3298)
    - RF 90103 - CHILD CARE PLUS and Supplementary Material, 1991-1998 (Box R3299)
- AC.2000.010: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1982-1999; AC.2000.010; 4.8 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3300-R3303.; 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3300-R3303.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.010.1
    - RF 91001 A 145 - UNIVERSITY OF NOTTINGHAM - RICE PROTOPLASTS, 1982-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3300)
    - RF 91003 A 94 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES -WIDE HYBRIDIZATION OF RICE, 1990-1997 (Box R3300)
    - RF 91003 A 119 - TRIBHUVAN UNIVERSITY - VIRUS DISEASES AND THEIR VECTORS IN NEPAL, 1991-1997 (Box R3300)
    - RF 91004 A 1 - DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH CENTER (CHINA) - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH PRIORITIES, 1991-1995 (Box R3300)
    - RF 91009 A 5 - INTERNATIONAL POTATO CENTER - INTENSIVE INPUT AGRICULTURE, 1989-1997 (Box R3301)
    - RF 91010 - HEALTH TRANSITION, 1987-1992; 1995; 1998; 4 folders. (Box R3301-R3302)
    - RF 91010 - HEALTH TRANSITION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1992; 1995; 1998; 3 folders. (Box R3301-R3302)
    - RF 91010 A 2 - NIGERIAN INSTITUTE OF SOCIAL AND ECONOMIC 'RESEARCH (NISER) - INEQUITABLE HEALTH OUTCOMES, 1988-1995; 1998-1999 (Box R3302)
    - RF 91013 A 490 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1988-1995; 1998; 2 folders. (Box R3302)
    - RF 91013 A 493 - RICE UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1988-1998 (Box R3303)
    - RF 91013 A 493 - RICE UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1998 (Box R3303)
    - RF 91029 A 6 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - GENETIC IMPROVEMENT OF CASSAVA, 1990-1997 (Box R3303)
    - RF 91031 A 297 - INTERNATIONAL CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY NETWORK (INCLEN)- EVALUATION, 1990-1993; 1996 (Box R3303)
    - RF 91031 A 329 - SUEZ CANAL UNIVERSITY - RISK FACTORS FOR BLADDER CANCER IN EGYPT, 1991-1994 (Box R3303)
    - RF 91031 A 333 - ADDIS ABABA UNIVERSITY - BIOSTATISTICS ON MEASLES IMMUNIZATION IN RURAL AREAS OF ETHIOPIA, 1991-1993; 1998 (Box R3303)
    - RF 91035 - ELECTRICAL ENERGY EFFICIENCY IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1991 (Box R3303)
    - RF 91037 A 238 - BAAH, JOHN - AFRICAN DISSERTATION INTERSHIP AWARD, 1990-1997 (Box R3303)
- AC.2000.020: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1986-1999; AC.2000.020; 6 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3304, R3306-R3309.; 5 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3304, R3306-R3309.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.020.1
    - RF 91055 A 138 - MENDOZA, DIEGO DE, 1990-1991; 1994-1997 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91055 A 145 - SIRIRURG SONGSIVILAI - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP, 1991-1995; 1998 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91055 A 149 - WORACHART SIRAWARAPORN - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP, 1991-1998 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91055 A 161 - FANG RONG-XIANG, 1987-1996 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91060 A 7 - WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY - IDENTIFICATION OF CASSAVA GENOTYPES, 1991-1997 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91061 A 19 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY - DENGUE VACCINE DEVELOPMENT PROJECT, 1986-1999 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91061 A 22 - INSTITUTO NACIONAL DE SALUD (COLOMBIA) ? TEST HUMAN RABIES VACCINE PRODUCED BY VECOL, 1992-1993 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91079 A 25 - KHON KAEN UNIVERSITY- STD/AIDS PREVENTION FOR THAI PROSTITUTES, 1991-1993 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91080A 137 - UNIVERSITY OF CAMBRIDGE - IMMUNITY AND MORBIDITY IN HUMAN SCHISTOSOMIASIS, 1988-1993 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91080 A 155 - AMERICAN SOCIETY OF TROPICAL MEDICINE AND HYGIENE - SUPPORT FOR ANNUAL MEETINGS, 1993-1996 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91080 A 161 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE FOR MALARIA RESEARCH IN MALI, 1992-1993 (Box R3304)
    - RF 91083 A 96 - WEBB, GLENN - DEMOGRAPHIC INNOVATION IN URBAN IBO COMMUNITY, 1991-1996 (Box R3304)
    - 920004-10 - CENTER FOR ENVIRONMENTAL AND AGRICULTURAL POLICY RESEARCH, EXTENSION AND DEVELOPMENT - RICE PRODUCTION CONSTRAINTS IN NEPAL, 1991-1996 (Box R3306)
    - 92004-11 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - FOOD RESEARCH INSTITUTE - PRIVATIZATION OF CHINESE RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1994-1995. 1998-1999 (Box R3306)
    - RF 92005 - INTERNATIONAL BIOSAFETY COMMISSION - GENETICALLY ENGINEERED ORGANISMS RISK AND BENEFITS, 1992. 1995 (Box R3306)
    - RF 92005 A 2 - STOCKHOLM ENVIRONMENT INSTITUTE (SEI) - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR ENVIRONMENTAL TECHNOLOGY AND MANAGEMENT - BIOTECHNOLOGY ADVISORY COMMISSION, 1991-1997 (Box R3306)
    - RF 92014 A 58 - BANARaS HINDU UNIVERSITY - PHOSPHORYLATION OF ANDROGEN RECEPTOR IN MALE PREPRODUCTIVE SYSTEM, 1991-1997 (Box R3306)
    - RF 92017 A 504 - INSTITUTO MORA - U.S. HISTORY PROJECT, 1991-1996 (Box R3306)
    - RF 92028 - HUMAN CAPITAL, 1987-1994; 1997; 3 folders. (Box R3306-R3307)
    - RF 92028 - HUMAN CAPITAL - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1994; 1997; 4 folders. (Box R3307)
    - RF 92033 - CHIANG MAl UNIVERSITY - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT - THAILAND, 1992-1995 (Box R3308)
    - RF 92034 A 381 - INCLEN, INC. - PHASE II ACTIVITIES IN LATIN AMERICA AND ASIA, 1991-1997 (Box R3308)
    - RF 92038 A 417 - ABARU, MILLIE - ADIA: CREDIT ACCESSIBILITY TO LOW-INCOME WOMEN IN UGANDA, 1992-1997 (Box R3308)
    - 920038-451 - MANU, ALHASSAN- ADIA: GROWTH AND STATUS OF INFANTS IN GHANA FED IMPROVED WEANING FOODS, 1994-1996 (Box R3308)
    - RF 92038 A 481 - OBOSU-MENSAH, KWAKU - ADIA: URBAN AGRICULTURE IN GHANA, 1995. 1998 (Box R3308)
    - RF 92042 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - PERSISTENT POVERTY IN URBAN AMERICA, 1988-1997; 4 folders. (Box R3308-R3309)
    - RF 92042 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - PERSISTENT POVERTY IN URBAN AMERICA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1997; 3 folders. (Box R3309)
- AC.2000.014: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1985-1999; AC.2000.014; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3305.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3305.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.014.1
    - RF 91083 A 116 - UNIVERSITY OF NEW MEXICO - EFFECTS OF SOAP OPERA IN TANZANIA ON FAMILY PLANNING, 1992-1999; 2 folders. (Box R3305)
    - RF 91089 A 19 - ZIMBABWE TEACHERS' ASSOCIATION - MICROCOMPUTER BASED LABS IN ZIMBABWE HIGH SCHOOLS, 1992-1995 (Box R3305)
    - RF 91090 A 85 - COUNCIL FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH IN AFRICA (SENEGAL) - DEMOCRATIC TRANSITIONS, 1995-1999 (Box R3305)
    - RF 91102 - MODERNIZING EDUCATOR TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT, 1991-1998 (Box R3305)
    - RF 92001 A 148 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - RICE MAPPING, 1995-1998 (Box R3305)
    - RF 92001 A 148 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - RICE MAPPING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1995-1998 (Box R3305)
- AC.2000.022: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-1998; AC.2000.022; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3310.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3310.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.022.1
    - 920055-79 - DEMBELE, NIAMA NANGO - SSRF: POLICY REFORM, MARKET RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT IN AGRICULTURE, 1993-1998 (Box R3310)
    - 920055-80 - DIAGNE, ALIOU - SSRF: RURAL CREDITS AND SAVINGS SYSTEMS, 1993-1998; 2 folders. (Box R3310)
    - 920055-81 - OLSON, JENNIFER MARIA - SSRF: INTEGRATION OF SOCIO-ECONOMIC AND BIOPHYSICAL DATA FOR CHARACTERIZATION IN THE EAST AFRICAN HIGHLANDS INITIATIVE, 1993-1998 (Box R3310)
    - RF 92059 A 162 - UNIVERSITY OF MAIDUGURI (NIGERIA) - PATHOGENESIS OF OVINE ABORTION CAUSED BY CHLAMYDIA PSITTACI, 1991-1995; 1998 (Box R3310)
    - RF 92059 A 169 - SHANDONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - BIOENGINEERED RESISTANCE OF RICE TO VIRAL INFECTION, 1992-1997 (Box R3310)
    - RF 92059 A 170 - INSTITUTO DE RECURSOS BIOLOGICOS -CIRN/INTA (ARGENTINA) - DETECTION OF DIAGNOSTIC MARKERS, 1991-1998 (Box R3310)
    - RF 92059 A 171 - SRINAKHARINWIROTE UNIVERSITY - SEPARATION OF NEUROPEPTIDES FROM NEMATODE ASCARIS, 1992-1996 (Box R3310)
    - RF 92059 A 173 - ESCOLA PAULISTA DE MEDICINA (BRAZIL) - TRANS-SIALIDASE GENE INACTIVATION IN TRYPANOSOMA CRUZ!, 1992-1998 (Box R3310)
    - RF 92059 A 174 - MAYORGA, LUIS S., 1989-1998 (Box R3310)
- AC.2000.023: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-1999; AC.2000.023; 4.8 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3311-R3314.; 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3311-R3314.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.023.1
    - RF 92059 A 178 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - ANCHORING YEAST ARTIFICIAL CHROMOSOMES AND CONSTRUCTING A PHYSICAL MAP OF RICE GENOME, 1992-1997 (Box R3311)
    - RF 92059 A 179 - AJOU UNIVERSITY (KOREA) - GENETIC MODIFICATION OF THE RICE GLUTELIN eDNA, 1992-1997 (Box R3311)
    - RF 92059 A 180 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE - MOLECULAR CHANGES IN THE GENOME OF RINDERPEST VIRUS, 1992-1998 (Box R3311)
    - RF 92060 A 3 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - STRIGA CONTROL, 1987-1996 (Box R3311)
    - RF 92060 A 15 - UNIVERSITY OF MYSORE (INDIA) - CROP GENETIC MAPPING/SORGHUM FELLOWSHIP, 1993-1995; 1998 (Box R3311)
    - RF 92060 A 19 - UNIVERSITY OF NEBRASKA - INTERNATIONAL SORGHUM/MILLET GENETIC IMPROVEMENT CONFERENCE, 1996-1998 (Box R3311)
    - RF 92068 - AFRICAN ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - CORE SUPPORT, 1987-1996; 3 folders. (Box R3311)
    - RF 92077 A 57 - CASE WESTERN RESERVE UNIVERSITY ? PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1986-1997; Total of 7 folders in Boxes R3312 and R3313 (Box R3312)
    - RF 92077 A 57 - CASE WESTERN RESERVE UNIVERSITY ? PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS, 1986-1997; Total of 7 folders in Boxes R3312 and R3313 (Box R3313)
    - RF 92077 A 57 - CASE WESTERN RESERVE UNIVERSITY ? PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1986-1997; Total of 3 folders in Boxes R3313 and R3314. (Box R3313)
    - RF 92077 A 57 - CASE WESTERN RESERVE UNIVERSITY ? PERSISTENT POVERTY PROJECTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1986-1997; Total of 3 folders in Boxes R3313 and R3314. (Box R3314)
    - RF 92087 A11 - CONCEPT FOUNDATION - REGISTER CYCLOFEM, 1992-1996 (Box R3314)
    - RF 92087 A 23 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD 'FEDERATION (ENGLAND) - NORPLANT STUDY IN PAKISTAN, 1992-1996 (Box R3314)
    - RF 92092 A 80 - MORRIS, MARTINA - SEXUAL NETWORKS AND HIV TRANSMISSION IN THAILAND AND UGANDA, 1994-1996 (Box R3314)
    - RF 92095 A 23 - SIERRA LEONE HOME ECONOMICS ASSOCIATION - SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY PROJECT FOR OUT-OF-SCHOOL YOUTH, 1992-1996 (Box R3314)
    - 920095-38 - LESOTHO SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS TEACHERS' ASSOCIATION - FAIR & WORKSHOP, 1994-1999 (Box R3314)
    - RF 92112 - NAACP LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - LITIGATION ACTIVITIES, 1991-1994 (Box R3314)
- AC.2000.025: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1988-1999; AC.2000.025; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3315-R3317.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3315-R3317.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.025.1
    - RF 92115 - UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO - CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF URBAN INEQUALITY, 1990-1997 (Box R3315)
    - RF 92115 - UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO - CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF URBAN INEQUALITY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-1997 (Box R3315)
    - RF 92119 - COLLEGE BOARD - PREPARE AT-RISK MINORITY STUDENTS IN MATHEMATICS COURSES, 1992-1998 (Box R3315)
    - RF 92119 - COLLEGE BOARD - PREPARE AT-RISK MINORITY STUDENTS IN MATHEMATICS COURSES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1992-1998 (Box R3315)
    - RF 92119 #4 - COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAMINATION BOARD - SATURDAY ACADEMIES - EQUITY 2000, 1989-1999 (Box R3316)
    - RF 92119 #4 - COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAMINATION BOARD - SATURDAY ACADEMIES - EQUITY 2000 - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1989-1999 (Box R3316)
    - RF 93001 A 193 - TRIBHUVAN UNIVERSITY (NEPAL) - VARIATION IN RICE TUNGRO VIRUS ISOLATES, 1993; 2000 (Box R3316)
    - RF 93003 A 172 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY OF THAILAND - MULTI-INSTITUTIONAL PROGRAM, 1988-1997 (Box R3316)
    - RF 93003 A 172 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY OF THAILAND - MULTI-INSTITUTIONAL PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3316)
    - RF 93003 A 190 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - TRAINING AND TECHNOLOGY TRANSFER FELLOWSHIPS, 1993-1997 (Box R3316)
    - RF 93003 A 198 - UNIVERSITY OF MADRAS - MOLECULAR PROBES TO ANALYZE XANTHOMONAS ORYZAE PV. ORYZAE IN INDIA, 1993-1994; 1007 (Box R3317)
    - RF 93003 A 206 - TATA INSTITUTE OF FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - MOLECULAR GENETICS OF INSECT OF RICE, 1988-1999 (Box R3317)
    - RF 93010 A 32 - LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT- LEADNET, 1993-1998 (Box R3317)
    - 930013-540 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - W.E.B. DU BOIS INSTITUTE - INTERNATIONAL AFRICAN-AMERICAN STUDIES ASSOCIATION, 1992-1996 (Box R3317)
    - RF 93018 A 8 - MUSEE DE LA CIVILISATION (CANADA) - "INGENIOUS AFRICA: ARTISANS AND RECYCLING" EXHIBITION, 1994-1996 (Box R3317)
    - RF 93018 A 8 - MUSEE DE LA CIVILISATION (CANADA) - "INGENIOUS AFRICA: ARTISANS AND RECYCLING" EXHIBITION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1996 (Box R3317)
    - RF 93022 A 183 - ODUOLA, AYOADE M. J., 1988-1998 (Box R3317)
    - RF 93022 A 184 - UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN (NIGERIA) - EPIDERMAL GROWTH FACTORS IN SPERMATOGENESIS, 1992-1999 (Box R3317)
    - RF 93022 A 187 - INSTITUTE OF CROP GERMPLASM RESOURCES (CHINA) - MOLECULAR MARKERS FOR ALIEN GENE TFANSFER, 1993-1998 (Box R3317)
- AC.2000.030: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-1999; AC.2000.030; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3318-R3319.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3318-R3319.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.030.1
    - RF 93022 A 188 - UNIVESIDADE FEDERAL DO RIO GRANDE DO SUL (BRAZIL) - STUDY OF SALMONELLA TYPHIMURIUM, 1992-1997 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93022 A 191 - INSTITUTO NACIONAL DE HIGIENE "RAFAEL RANGEL" (VENEZUELA) - STUDY OF MOLECULAR EPIDEMIOLOGY OF GUANARITO VIRUS, 1992-1997 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93022 A 193 - BEIJING INSTITUTE FOR CANCER RESEARCH (CHINA) - STUDY OF IN VITRO MODEL GASTRIC CARCINOGENESIS, 1992-1997 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93022 A 197 - TATA INSTITUTE OF FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH NATIONAL CENTRE FOR BIOLOGICAL SCIENCES (INDIA) - MOLECULAR ANALYSIS OF OLFACTORY TRANSDUCTION IN DROSOPHILA MELANOGASTER, 1992-1998 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93022 A 198 - TATA INSTITUTE OF FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH NATIONAL CENTRE FOR BIOLOGICAL SCIENCES (INDIA) - HOST FACTORS IN HUMAN PAPILLOMAVIRUS, 1992-1998 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93022 A 199 - VIKRAM UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - HOST RESPONSES TO VACCINATION AGAINST HELMINTH INFECTIONS, 1993-1997 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93022 A 202 - INSTITUTE OF BIOTECHNOLOGY - NATIONAL CENTER FOR NATURAL SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY (VIETNAM) - MOLECULAR CLONING AND CHARACTERIZATION OF RICE GENES, 1991-1997 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93027 A 416 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - SOCIAL SCIENCE CONTINUING EDUCATION PROJECT WITHIN INCLEN, 1992-1997 (Box R3318)
    - 930027-422 - INCLEN, INC.- PHARMACOEPIDEMIOLOGY BIOSTATISTICS, AND COMMUNITY-BASED UNDERGRADUATE CURRICULUM, 1994-1997 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93029 A 5 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF NUTRITION SALVADOR ZUBIRAN (MEXICO) - TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN FERTILITY REGULATIONS, 1993-1997 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93031 A 371 - MANDIRINGANA, OWEN T. - ADIA: WATER AND SOLUTE MOVEMENT IN SOILS, 1993-1994 (Box R3318)
    - RF 93031 A 402 - APPLETON, NATHANIEL S.- ADIA: SMALLHOLDER RESOURCE MANAGEMENT STRATEGIES IN CAMEROON, 1993-1995 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 A 406 - OJIAMBO, SWIRE S. - ADIA: STUDY SUBSURFACE WATER OUTFLOW, 1993-1997 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 A 408 - KARANU FRANCIS - ADIA PROTECTIVE IMMUNINITY AGAINST HAEMONCHUS CONTORTUS, 1993-1999 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 A 513 - RUBIIK, GEORGE- ADIA: COMMUNAL ETHIC, EGALITARIAN IDEOLOGY AND AGRARIAN TRANSFORMATION IN KENYA, 1995-1996 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 A 515 - MTIKA MIKE - ADIA: ILLNESS DEATHS AND FOOD SECURITY IN MALAWI, 1994-1997 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 A 520 - EJOBOWAH, BOYR - ADIA: "THE POLITICAL PUBLIC AND DIFFERENCE: THE CASE OF NIGERIA", 1994-1999 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 A 529 - MUTANDI, ROBSON - ADIA: PASTORAL COMMUNITIES IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1994-1999 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 A 532 - FISSEHA, ABEBE- ADIA: ETHIOPIAN SECONDARY EDUCATION, 1941-1991, 1995-1997 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 #548 - GABRE-MADHIN, ELENI - ADIA: "ETHIOPIAN GRAIN MARKETS ACROSS SPACE AND TIME", 1996-1997 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 #552 - IDRIS, ALI - ADIA: CHARACTERIZATION OF THREE WHITEFLY-TRANSMITTED VIRUSES AFFECTING TOMATOES FROM SUDAN, 1995-1998 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93031 #561 - MULAUDZI, MAANDA- ADIA: AGRARIAN TRANSFORMATION IN RURAL SOUTH AFRICA 1900-1990s, 1995-1997 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93038 A 26 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - NUTRIENT RECYCLING IN FARMING SYSTEMS IN EMBU DISTRICT, 1993-1997 (Box R3319)
    - 930038-36 - KENYA FORESTRY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - PRODUCTIVITY ASPECTS OF CALLIANDRA CALOTHYRSUS, 1991-1997 (Box R3319)
    - RF 93039 A 75 - CROWLEY, EVE LAKSHMI - SSRF: OPPORTUNITY AND INVESTMENT IN BIOLOGICAL RESOURCES AND SOIL MANAGEMENT, 1992-1998 (Box R3319)
    - 930039-77 - BENSON, TODD DAVID - SSRF: IMPROVEMENT OF MAIZE PRODUCTIVITY, 1993-1998 (Box R3319)
    - 930039-84 - SOULE, MEREDITH JEAN - SSRF: CONCEPTUAL FRAMEWORK FOR ICRAF'S TECHNOLOGY TESTING PROJECT, 1993-1998 (Box R3319)
- AC.2000.031: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-1998; AC.2000.031; 7.2 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3320, R3320A, R3321-R3324.; 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3320, R3320A, R3321-R3324.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF) - General, AC.2000.031.1
    - RF 93040 A 15 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE- CROP SCIENCE, 1991-1998 (Box R3320)